{
    "subject": "resource/Serbian_Vojvodina",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Zrenjanin",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Serbian Vojvodina is Zrenjanin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9601222276687622,
            "question": "Which Serbian province has Zrenjanin as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9428724646568298,
            "question": "What is the capital of Serbian Vojvodina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8697723150253296,
            "question": "Is Zrenjanin a city in Serbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8277812004089355,
            "question": "Is Zrenjanin a major city in Serbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6582131385803223,
            "question": "What administrative region is Zrenjanin the capital of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.643571674823761,
            "question": "Where is Zrenjanin located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5334293246269226,
            "question": "Name one city in Vojvodina."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5055369138717651,
            "question": "What is the name of the province that includes Zrenjanin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2604641616344452,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Vojvodina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09251970052719116,
            "question": "Does Serbia have multiple provinces?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Serbian Vojvodina is Zrenjanin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9328_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Vojvodina?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9328_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the province that includes Zrenjanin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9328_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one city in Vojvodina.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9328_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9328_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Zrenjanin is a significant city in Vojvodina, they do not claim it to be the capital.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe query asks whether the capital of Serbian Vojvodina is Zrenjanin. However, according to the context information provided, Zrenjanin is described as a city located in the eastern part of Vojvodina, Serbia (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9328/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt), and its population data suggests that it is not the capital. In fact, Novi Sad is mentioned as one of the largest cities in Vojvodina (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9328/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt), suggesting that it may be the capital or at least a major city. Therefore, the answer is \"no\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Zrenjanin, including its location and population data, but they do not mention that it is the capital of Serbian Vojvodina. Novi Sad and Subotica are mentioned as larger cities in Vojvodina, but there's no explicit statement indicating that Zrenjanin is the capital."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Zrenjanin is a city located in Vojvodina, Serbia, but it is not the capital of Vojvodina. Novi Sad is the capital of Vojvodina.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several texts state Novi Sad is the third largest city in Vojvodina.  Additionally, some texts mention Zrenjanin being the administrative center of the Central Banat District, not the entire province.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the capital of Serbian Vojvodina is actually Novi Sad, not Zrenjanin.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Zrenjanin is not the capital of Vojvodina; it is described as the administrative centre of the Central Banat District, and Novi Sad is mentioned as a larger city in Vojvodina.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}